## SHAUNA NAOMI LARKIN

# P.O. Box 325, 1035 Biddle St ●Georgetown, CO 80444 ●snlarkin46@gmail.com

Over the course of nine years owning my own business, and the five years I have spent working in customer service centered careers I have focused on exceeding my customer's expiations. I believe the knowledge and skills I have developed during that time along with my recent and ongoing time spent in University of Denver's Web Development: Boot Camp would serve me will in the transitioning to work for you growing business.

In the course of my career, I've developed a number of important skills that will help me succeed in this new role. I have proven I never back down from a hard task by a strong record of exceeding goals, expectations, and special expertise in my ability to work with people, and defuse stressful situations. My experience and educational background have prepared me for this career move and some key proficiency I can bring to this role is:

- Strong verbal communication skills, customer service skills.
- Work effectively within a group and independently with minimal supervision.
- Detail orientated and organized with great time management/ scheduling.
- Technical savvy with the ability to easily adapt to new software.

My attached resume further highlights the attributes that I would bring to this position. I am confident that I can make an immediate positive contribution to your organization which will help your organization achieve its goals.

Thank you for your time and consideration. I am looking forward to speaking with you further regarding this position.

Thank you,

Shauna Naomi Larkin

#### **Career Summary**

Work experience in secretarial position for a government agency and private business. Customer service centered jobs in the private, public, and government sectors. Seven years of running my own pet care business, in my local community growing it to fit the needs of my community and clients.

#### Skills/Qualifications

•	Detail orientated and organized.	•	REST API queries, 3 <sup>rd</sup> party JS and CSS library integration, deployment of web
•	Time management/ scheduling.		
· ·	Easily adapt to changes.  Sales and customer service both in retail and service business.  Multi-tasking of multiple projects in a busy work environment.  Work effectively within a group and independently with minimal	•	Node.js, Express servers, REST API creation  Test Driven Development with Jest, mySQL, Object Oriented Programming, JQuery  Quick to learn and understand new
•	independently with minimal supervision.  Strong verbal communication skills go getter.  Technical skills to solve and diagnose problems.		software.  Strong knowledge and understanding of Microsoft Office Suite and Adobe Acrobat Pro and the Adobe suites collection of software.  Colorado Public Notary.
•	Computer competency in both PC and MAC systems.	•	GitHub account  https://github.com/waterylime
•	Proficient in using iPad, iPhone, and other smart phones and tablets.		mipon galactions were juice
•	HTML, CSS, JavaScript		

#### Education

 University of Denver Web Development: Boot Camp

Red Rocks Community College
 Associates of Liberal Arts

 Clear Creek High School High School Diploma August 2019 - March 2020

2013 - 2016

2002-2006

### Coding Experience and Select Projects:

Dragon Restaurant: a full stack app that simulates table reservation for a restaurant with limited tables. When a reservation is made, details are posted to an API. The table availability is dynamically updated on the corresponding page, and the API data. This was a collaborative project hosted on these links: https://github.com/tzvik15/Hot-restauraunt-cold-food (repository), https://sheltered-bayou-19458.herokuapp.com/ (deployed).

Book Finder: is an app in which you enter the name of book or author, you are returned suggestions of other books along with a synopsis of the story. Suggested books are then linked to Google Books where you can read a preview of the book, and if available the New York Times review of the book. <a href="https://github.com/waterylime/Book-Finder">https://github.com/waterylime/Book-Finder</a> (respository), <a href="https://waterylime.github.io/Book-Finder">https://waterylime.github.io/Book-Finder</a> (deployed).

#### **Experience**

Carlson & Carlson Attorneys at Law, P.C.- Paralegal Supervisor Steven O'Connor

March 2018 to March 2019

• Prepared, served and filed documents with the Court for family, criminal, probate, and civil.

- Communicate with client.
- Preparing for trials, hearings and Municipal Court.
- General office duties answering the phones, scheduling meetings, scanning, copying, and correspondence
- Maintaining and organizing reference files, and client files.
- Archiving of legal documents.
- Drafting of estate packages

O'Dell & Silburn, LLC – Administrative Assistant/Legal Assistant

September 2016-March 2018

- Supervisor Christopher C. O'Dell
- Archiving of legal documents.Filling of documents and bills.
- Technical support.
- Support to Para legal with secretarial work.
- · Research and preparation for cases.
- Accounting for conservatorship.

**Clear Creek County Site Development Department** – Administrative Assistant Supervisor John Loughrey

2014-July 2016

- · Front counter secretary, answer phones help the customer in the process of submitting building permits.
- Work in TrakIT, to keep track of all permits.
- Make all handouts, informational flyers, and permit applications for distribution to the general public.
- Prepare and review documents prior to submittal for the county commissioner hearings.
- Run monthly budget and permit status reports, and prepare expirations notices.
- Do historical and current research for projects in any department.
- · Handle all pledge and securities for two departments.
- Work with Eagle Recorder and Clear Creek Assessor software.
- Scan, copy, file, in and outgoing mail and all other secretarial duties.
- Conduct site visits.

Pampered Pets - Owner

2009-present

- Created inventory and information sheet to ensure seamless consistent care and wellbeing of house and pet during owner's absences.
- Provided quality care, exercise, and socialization for pets of various temperaments.
- Quality service for discerning customers.
- Positive reinforcement training.

Lark Trucking - Bookkeeper

January 2006- 2015

Supervisor Iris White

- · Keeping books for tax records on Quick books.
- · Balancing all accounts.
- Organizing and maintaining all records need for business operations.
- Creating year end reports and preparing all documents for taxes.

References

Sara Switzer Honorably discharged Veteran ~15 years of acquaintance ~

John Romeo Client of my business~13 years of acquaintance ~